Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Press and publicity, 1914-2010; 1983-2010; Series 13
  - Sigmar Polke Checklist, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Sigmar Polke: Photoworks Wall Text, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Sigmar Polke Clippings, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - [Moscow Studio], Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Moscow Studio Press Release, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Moscow Studio Background, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Moscow Studio Images, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Moscow Studio Clippings, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Exhibition Background, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Exhibitionn Press Release, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Exhibition Images (empty), Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Exhibition Clippings (empty), Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Faculty 1996, Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - David Mordini Background, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - David Mordini Press Release (empty)), Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - David Mordini Images, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - David Mordini Clippings, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - [Mordini Press and Slides], Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - [Faberge Press and Stickers], Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Faberge and Finland Checklist, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Faberge and Finland Images, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Faberge and Finland Clippings, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Faberge and Finland Press Release, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Faberge and Finland Background, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - [Faberge Press], Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Two From Flanders 1995, Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Washinigton Velvets Press Clippings, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - [Two From Flanders Invites], Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Jackson Jarvis Images, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Martha Jackson - Jarvis Release, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Martha Jackson - Jarvis Checklist, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Martha Jarvis Jackson Background, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - [Jarvis Loose], Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Recent Acquisitions Release, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 43)
  - Martha Jackson - Jarvis Press Clippings, Circa 1996; Series 13 (Box 82, Folder 44)
  - Regional Scholastic Exhibition Press Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Regional Scholastic Exhibition Images, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Regional Scholastic Exhibition Background, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Regional Scholastic: Checklist, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Regional Scholastic Exhibition: Press Release, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - The Peale Family: Creation of an American Legacy, 1997 April 26-July 6; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Peale Family Images, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Peale Family Press Release, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Peale Family Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Peale Family Background, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Peale Family - Object Checklist, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Jamieson Event, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Joshua Johnston Images, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Joshua Johnston Background, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Picasso: Release, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Picasso: Checklist, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Picasso: Background, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Picasso: Images, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Picasso: Press Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Lois Mailon Jones, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Impressions from Nature Press Release, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Impressions from Nature Background, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Impressions from Nature Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Impressions from Nature Label/Wall Text, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Impressions from Nature Checklist, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - The Painted Sketch, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Impressions from Nature Label Text, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - 98 Art Auction Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - 98 Art Auction Background, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - 98 Art Auction Images, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Janet Clips, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Milt Hinton Press Release, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Milt Hinton Background, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Milt Hinton Images, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Milt Hinton Clippings, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Chihuly Over Venice Press Release, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Chihuly Over Venice Images, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - [Chihuly], Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Chihuly Release, 1996 February 17; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Dale Chihuly Press Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Chihuly Background, 1996 February 17; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Chihuly Over Venice Background, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Chihuly Over Venice Images, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Chihuly Over Venice Clippings, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Chihuly Over Venice Wall Text/Label Text, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Jazz Series, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Cafe, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Perm. Collection, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Education, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Janet, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Listings, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - [Listings Continued], Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - [Listings Continued], Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Best Worst, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Mentions, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - WPA/Corcoran, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Music Series, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Shop, Circa 1991-1999; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Jyung Mee Park, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Jyung Mee Park, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Jyung Mee Park, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Jyung Mee Park, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - New Worlds from Old: Press Release, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - New Worlds from Old: Images, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - New Worlds from Old: Label/Wall Text, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - New Worlds from Old: Checklist, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - New Worlds Contract, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Australian Landscapes, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Australia Folder Design, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - New Worlds from Old: Background, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - New Worlds from Old: News Articles, 1998; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - New Worlds from Old, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - New Worlds from Old: Photo Images, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - New Worlds from Old: Australian Press Kits, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - New Worlds from Old: Clippings, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Australian Embassy, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Art Express, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - The Ambiguity of Fuzzy, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - WPA/C's "Fuzzy" Clippings, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Reuben Nakian Checklist, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Reuben - Washington Post/Times, 1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Reuben Nakian Label / Wall Text, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Nakian Exhibition, 1996-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Reuben Nakian Images, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - BFA - Spring 1999 Clippings, 1999 March 5-12; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - WPA / Corcoran Exhibitions, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - WPA / Corcoran Residue: Press Release, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - WPA / Corcoran Residue, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Mentions, Circa 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - [Openings/Mentions (1 of 3)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - [Openings/Mentions (2 of 3)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - [Openings/Mentions (3 of 3)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - [Staff 1991], Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - [David Levy, Board, Susan Rosenbaum, J. Cowart, Kazimir, Foresta], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - [Perm. Collection (1 of 2)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - [Perm. Collection (2 of 2)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - [Past Exhibits (1 of 4)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - [Past Exhibits (2 of 4)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - [Past Exhibits (3 of 4)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - [Past Exhibits (4 of 4)], 1991; Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - [Mentions 1991 (1 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - [Mentions 1991 (2 of 2)], Series 13 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - 1999 Janet's Clips, Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - 1999 Mentions, Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - 1999 Listings, Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Amadeo de Souza Cardosa, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Souza Cardoso: Images, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Catalogue Contents, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Amadeo de Souza Cardosa Label/Wall Text (empty), Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Amadeo de Souza Cardoso Press Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Amadeo de Souza Cardoso Background, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Amadeo de Souza Cardoso Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Amadeo de Souza Cardoso Checklist (empty), Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Arnold Newman Press Kits, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Sponsor Letters, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Arnold Newman Images, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Arnold Newman Checklist, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Arnold Newman: Original Images Agreement, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Arnold Newman: Press Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Arnold Newman, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Newman Ads, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Arnold Newman Background, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Arnold Newman Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Lists/Media, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Arnold Newman, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Bus, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Museum Bus Clips/Ads, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Charisma, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Violins of Lafayette, 1998; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Violins of Lafayette, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Musical Evening Series1996 Press Clippings, Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - [Romanovs Slides], Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Annie Leibowitz: Women Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - The Way Home: Ending Homelessness Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - Propoganda and Dreams Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - Developing Illusions Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - FIVA Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - Gordon Parks Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 36)
  - Hospice Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 37)
  - Lichtenstein Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 13 (Box 94, Folder 38)
  - [Slides], Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran Alumni Hemicycle Exhibition 1999 Press Release, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - [Alliancce for Young Artists and Writers], Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Embody Disembody 5/1999, 1999 May; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Chimney Sweep, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Hemicycle Media Alert Faxs, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Hemicycle - "Corcoran Community", Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Hemicycle Mobil Renovation Release, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Advance Hemicycle Releasae 1992, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Hemicycle Exhibition Schedule '93, 1993; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - VACOP, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - College Clips 1999, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - VACOP, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - VACOP, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - VACOP 1997, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - VACOP Clippings 1996, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - VACOP, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - College Clips 1998, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - School 1997, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Corcoran School Clippings 1996, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - School Press Clippings 1994, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - VACOP Clippings 1999, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - School Benefit June 11, 1992, 1992 June 11; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Beaux-Arts Masquerade Ball, 1995 March 4; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - School Benefit Release '96, 1996; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Beaux Arts Masquerade, Circa 1992-1999; Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - HUD Project 1994, Series 13 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Sam Bookatz Images, 1999; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Sam Bookatz Clippings, 1999; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Sam Bookatz Release, 1999; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Bookatz - prerss kits, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Speak Truth To Power - press kits, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Speak Truth To Power: Checklist, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Speak Truth To Power: Press Release, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Speak Truth To Power: Bckground, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Speak Truth To Power: Images, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Speak Truth To Power, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Speak Truth To Power: Clippings, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Speak Truth To Power: Slides, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Speak Truth To Power: Slides, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Advanced Exhibition Schedule, 1993-1996; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Larry Sultan - Tour Itinerary, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Larry Sultan - wall text, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Larry Sultan images, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Larry Sultan - Background, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Larry Sultan - checklist, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Larry Sultan - biographical info., Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Larry Sultan Press Clippings, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Larry Sultan - Press Release, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Larry Sultan - *ress Clippings, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Louise Bourgeois - Background, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Bourgeois - checklist, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Bourgeois - about the artist, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Bourgeois - programs at a glance, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Terrie's Statement, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Bourgeois - about the Curator, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Bourgeois - Press Release, Circa 1993-2000; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Here is NY Ads:, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Here is New York: Originals, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Here is NY: Printed Materials, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Here is NY: Press Kits, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Here is NY: Press Release, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Here is NY: Info., Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Here is NY: News Clippings, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Lou Stovall, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - 46th Biennial Clippings, 2000; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Vik Muniz, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Jimmy Johnson, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - David Chung, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Shimon Attie, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Jennifer Steinkamp, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Biennial: clippings, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - The 46th Biennial Exhibition: Media/Metaphor - press kits, 2000 December 9 - 2001 March 5; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Biennial, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Biennial: images, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Rovner Film, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Biennial Reproductions, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Biennial: Press Release, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Goldyne - background, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Goldyne - checklist, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - Goldyne - press release, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - Goldyne - images, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - Goldyne - clippings, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - Wall Text - Goldyne, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - Poetry and Alchemy - press kits, 2001 October 6 - December 17; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - Ewald Images, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - Street Games: Wendy Ewald - press kits, 2002 January 19 - April 8; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 30)
  - Bessie Potter Vonnoh, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - Vonnoh - Clips, Circa 2000-2002; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - Stanley Tretick: The Kennedy Years - press kits, 2002 July 1 - October 7; Series 13 (Box 110, Folder 33)
  - Frank O. Gehry Slide Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Frank O. Gehry Slide Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran Year in Review, 1998-1999; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Santiago Calatrava Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Santiago Calatrava, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Daniel Libeskind, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Libeskin Images, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Sir Norman Foster Wins Architecture Prize, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Gehry Sketches, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Project Facts, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Gehry / Architecture Releases, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Gehry Background / Other Commissions, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Architectural Press / Materials, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Gift Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Gehry Clips 1999, Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Gehry Clips 2000, Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Gehry Clips 2001, Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Gehry Clips 2002, Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Gehry Clips 2003, Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Gehry Clips 2004, Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Architectural Press / Materials, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Gehry: Clips, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Gehry: Background, Circa 1998-2004; Series 13 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - College Clips, 2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - In Process Originals, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Madeleine Keesing, 2002; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - 2001 The Eyes of History Contract Records, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - 2001 Eyes of History Original Press List Materials, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Eyes of History, 2001 May - 2001 June; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - 2001 The Eyes of History WHNPA Exhibition, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Tara Donovan, Hemicycle 1999 Release, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Tara Donovan, Hemicycle 1999 Clippings, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Tara Donovan Images Hemicycle 1999, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Tara Donovan Background, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Hemicycle Brochures, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Homeland Clips, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Mary Frank Lecture, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Off the Wall, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - VACOP - Info, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - VACOP, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - VACOP Community Outreach, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - NEA Coming Up Taller Award, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - CASA Event, 1999 October 8; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Commencement 2000, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - FOCUS Press Release, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Alumni/Peru Embassy, 2000 August; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - VACOP Earth Day Pitches, 2001 April 22; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Faculty/Staff Art Events, 2000-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Art Reach Press Release, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - Sammy Hoi - Departure Relase, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 27)
  - Armin and Dorothea Hofmann Hemicycle Release, 1999; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 28)
  - Armin Dorothea Hofmann Hemicycle Images, 1999; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 29)
  - Expressions: Art by DC Youth, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 30)
  - 2000 Societe Imaginaire Exhibition, Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 31)
  - Student/Faculty Artwork, Circa 1999-2001; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 32)
  - New Association BFA Dean - Denise Mullen, 2000; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 33)
  - Papermaking Show (1st National Collegiate Juried Handmade Paper Art Show), 2000 August; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 34)
  - All Senior Exhibition, 2000; Series 13 (Box 131, Folder 35)